<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Modules xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK0" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="3/31/2008">
    <Title>Consolidated Consolidates</Title>
    <Body>It seems as though investors and the market in general approve of the changes at the top of Consolidated Holdings&apos; (Stock0) board this week. New CEO Isabella Price is well respected in the industry, and her speech at the extraordinary general meeting yesterday reveals how she intends to turn the company around this year by disposing of loss-making properties, investing in new sites, and exerting stronger management of subcontractors and developers. &quot;The recent disasters the occurred under the management of disgraced previous CEO Milton Albury are a thing of the past,&quot; she said. Optimistic signs include Consolidated&apos;s share price growing by over 15% already this week, with no sign of slowing.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK0" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="12/6/2007">
    <Title>Albury&apos;s Career Buried at Board Meeting</Title>
    <Body>Surprising news over the weekend as Consolidated Holdings (Stock0) CEO Milton Albury is forced out of the company at an emergency board meeting on Saturday morning. Albury has overseen a series of disasters at the property management corporation, including a shopping mall so poorly constructed that the operators were unable to obtain a permit, an office block built to &quot;an exciting new design paradigm&quot; that turned out to be uninhabitable, and delays (reported this week) with their new state-of-the-art office block in Jamaica. Vice chairman Isabella Price is expected to take over as CEO. Her experience and hands-on approach were welcomed by the market, and shares are expected to rise dramatically when trading resumes on Monday.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK0" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="5/24/2006">
    <Title>Hot (and Windowless) Under the Collar</Title>
    <Body>More questions are being raised at Consolidated Holdings (Stock0) as news surfaces of problems with their largest off-shore investment. The hi-tech 68-storey tower block being constructed in Jamaica, which should have been fully occupied last month, still has no glass in the windows and no air conditioning. Supply difficulties, combined with bad weather, are reported to be the reason, but the ongoing loss of rental income is hurting margins and is likely to have a considerable impact on the share price. It looks like another disaster that Consolidated can ill afford, and is already prompting questions about the stewardship of the company under CEO Milton Albury. Critics suggest that his previous post as junior executive at toymaker Fitness Toys has not provided him with the experience required to run a multi-billion dollar organization such as Consolidated.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK0" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="2/14/2005">
    <Title>Desperate Consolidated Holdings</Title>
    <Body>Continuing increases in raw material costs are hitting profitability at all property management corporations, and Consolidated Holdings (Stock0) have not been able to buck the trend. Published figures for the previous three months show falling rental receipts and lower than forecast income. Spokesperson Catherine Abel, speaking to members of a local property investment organization in Memphis on Monday evening, suggested that builders are losing confidence in their ability to rent or sell new corporate office blocks. During questions afterwards, Abel insisted that Consolidated would not be selling off assets, and would continue to invest for the future.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK2" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="3/31/2008">
    <Title>Great Lakes Goes Healthy</Title>
    <Body>It looks like the new range of healthy products Great Lakes Food Market (Stock2) introduced last month are a hit with shoppers, driving profits at the processed food supplier and pushing share prices up by almost 16%. CEO Roy Srini, speaking to reporters on Monday at the Texas &quot;National Good Eating&quot; festival, said that consumer preferences are changing, and shoppers are taking more interest in the ingredients of the processed foods they buy. &quot;We have halved the number of artificial flavourings and colorants we use across the whole line of our trademark pasta burgers,&quot; he told the 18,000-strong audience. &quot;In fact, we replaced 17 chemicals just by adding salt and pepper, and it actually tasted better.&quot; However, rumors that they are carrying out experiments using burger rolls made from ordinary bread, rather than their own secret recipe that includes over 29 artificial and undocumented ingredients, were robustly denied.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK2" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="12/6/2007">
    <Title>Ravioli Scare Prompts Government Action</Title>
    <Body>Just as they are recovering from supply difficulties in Italy, Great Lakes Food Market (Stock2) has been hit by a new emergency resolution handed down by central Government yesterday. The cross-party investigative group Standards for American Unhealthy Consumables Explorative (SAUCE) is unhappy about Great Lakes&apos; new product, and is seeking clarification on calorie and fat content. The Ravioli Double Sausage Cheeseburger, which contains over three pounds of fried ravioli, is flavoured with several suspect artificial ingredients that the Government committee is determined to ban. Great Lakes&apos; spokesperson Jennifer White, who attended the committee meeting, insists that their products are wholesome and safe, and that removing the artificial flavorings will damage the integrity of the product. &quot;We are concerned that SAUCE may ruin the flavour of our burgers&quot; she said.</Body>
  </NewsItem>
  <NewsItem TickerSymbol="STOCK2" IconUri="/StockTraderRI.Modules.News;Component/Data/Images/Annotation_New.png" PublishedDate="5/24/2006">
    <Title>It&apos;s Pasta La Vista for Great Lakes</Title>
    <Body>Great Lakes Food Market (Stock2) is back in profit after the major loss of income from damaged crops. New sources of their mainstay raw material, spaghetti, are coming on stream and within days they expect the shortages of the last few months to be a thing of the past. Purchasing controller Robyn Munoz, speaking during a trip to visit new suppliers in Italy, insisted that there is already enough spaghetti in transit to the Texas factory satisfy the growing demand for their trademark Bolognaise Burgers product. He told reporters &quot;The public no longer need to worry about shortages, and panic buying will soon come to an end once shoppers see full shelves at their local supermarket.&quot; Meanwhile, the news drove share prices up by 35 cents.</Body>
  </NewsItem>

</Modules>